There is no turning back
The Village is a drama, mystery, thriller film directed by M. Night Shyamalan.
When a willful young man tries to venture beyond his sequestered Pennsylvania hamlet, his
actions set off a chain of chilling incidents that will alter the community forever.
Ivy Walker, played by Bryce Dallas Howard.
Lucius Hunt, played by Joaquin Phoenix.
Noah Percy, played by Adrien Brody.
Edward Walker, played by William Hurt.
Alice Hunt, played by Sigourney Weaver.
August Nicholson, played by Brendan Gleeson.
The Village (marketed as M.
Night Shyamalan's The Village) is a 2004 American period
thriller film written, produced, and directed by M.
Night Shyamalan.
It stars Bryce Dallas Howard, Joaquin Phoenix, Adrien Brody,
William Hurt, Sigourney Weaver, and Brendan Gleeson.
The story is about a village whose population lives in fear
of creatures inhabiting the woods beyond it.
The Village received mixed reviews and grossed $256.7 million worldwide.
James Newton Howard was nominated for Best Original
Score at the 77th Academy Awards.
The film explores themes of pennsylvania, usa,
twist, forest, rural area, blindness.
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.